Lawrence Guyot, Jr. 130
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - Redevelopment Land Agency Revitalization Corporation, 2000-2003 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization, 1989-1998 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - District of Columbia Historic Preservation Plan, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Stand Up! Documentary Council on African American Affairs Contact List, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Study Circles Resource Center, 1999-2007 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Federal Review of Voting Changes, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Ward One Voter List, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - City Within a City: Greater U Street Heritage Trail, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - United States District Court for the District of Columbia Robert Robbins v. Ronald Reagan, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Institute of Social Studies Post-Graduate Diploma Programme: Children, Youth and Development, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights Board of Director's Meeting Agenda, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - The School of Governance Act of 1999 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights Last Board Meeting, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Information on Power Plants, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - New York Avenue Metrorail Station: Environmental Assessment and Section 4(f) Evaluation, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights Personnel Manual and Office Procedures Manual, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Proposal for the Redevelopment of 1431 and 35 Chapin Street Northwest (Parcel 32) by Chapin Heights Partners, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 2002-2004 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 2000-2003 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B 1 of 2, 1999-2004 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B 2 of 2, 1999-2004 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Columbia Heights, 1999-2002 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 1997-2003 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Government of the District of Columbia Office of the Inspector General, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - District of Columbia Board of Zoning Adjustment, 2000-2003 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 2000-2003 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics, 2000-2003 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - District of Columbia Alcoholic Beverage Regulation Administration, 2003-2004 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 2000-2004 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency Revitalization Corporation Board Minutes, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Uptown Destination District Scope, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - The Public Welfare Foundation, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - North Capitol Neighborhood Development Inc., 2001 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - North Capitol Collaborative Inc. 2004 Mini-Grant Application (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - District of Columbia Taekwondo Association Mini-Grants Application, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Implementing the Help America Vote Act: Helping Avoid Discrimination, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - United States District Court for the District of Columbia: Gloria A. Halcomb vs. William Pickle, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Barack Obama vs Hillary Clinton Presidential Primary Newsclippings, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Anthony A. William - Announcement, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Voter Registration, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - ODR: The Structure of Change, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Foldered Printed Materials, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 2002-2004 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights Board of Directors Briefing Book Parcel 34, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - The Reformer Building: 100 Years Programs, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Medicare Matters Newspaper, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - DCT 1000 Cable Terminal Installation Manual, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - The Economic Resurgence of Washington DC: Citizens Plan for Prosperity in the 21st Century 1 of 2, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - The Economic Resurgence of Washington DC: Citizens Plan for Prosperity in the 21st Century 2 of 2, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Black Enterprise Magazine, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Labor Market Research and Information, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Federal Review of Voting Changes, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - D.C. Board of Elections and Ethics, 2000-2003 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Combatting the Terrorism of Illiteracy II, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Help America Vote Act of 2002 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - DC Democracy Fund (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - DC Democracy Fund (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2011 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Flyers and Brochures, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Salute to D.C. Military and Statehood Veterans, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - This Light of Ours, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commisson, 2000-2005 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Neighborhood Action Citizen Summit IV, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Community Development, 2000-2002 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - News/Magazines/Articles, 1989-2011 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Putting the Movement Back Into Civil Rights Teaching, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Loose Printed Material, 2004-2011 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Dr. Earnest Simo, 1994-2001 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Legal Documents, 1969-2003 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers Are Not the Solution for DC, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Pacifica Radio, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - DRAFT Traffic Calming Study, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - News Clippings, 1999-2010 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Gore/Lieberman Inc., 2000 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Fair Budget Coalition of the District of Columbia, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Photographs, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 24)